Ajiri Iviero

PYTHON BACK-END DEVELOPER

Recent completion a 1-year intensive personal development program. Skilled in coding focus, communication, goal setting, adapting to tech changes, and problem-solving. Committed to positive team collaboration, and continuous learning. Integrates personal development for a successful career.

ajconnectprime@gmail.com +49 1601147151 | Bei Berlin, Germany

linkedin.com/in/ajiri-michael

github.com/ajconnects 🕠

stackoverflow.com/users/20775598/aj-connect-plus

EDUCATION

PYTHON BACK-END PROGRAMMING

DCI Digital Career Institution GmbH

08/2023 - Present

Berlin, Germany

Courses

 Completed a one-yearfull-time training including Python Basic, Database, Django and Flask Framework. Taking German Lesson during the course.

Bachelor of Science, Economics, B.ScDelta State University

07/2011 - 09/2015

Delta State, Nigeria

WORK EXPERIENCE

Migration To Germany

To Start New Career.

03/2022 - 02/2023

Berlin, Germany

Software Engineer A.M.A Mike Global Resources Ltd

09/2019 - 02/2022

Abuja, Nigeria

Software Programmer.

Achievements/Tasks

- Diagnose and resolve hardware and software issues.
- Ensure Proper functioning of all systems.
- Maintain accurate records of system activities, issues, and resolutions.

Computer Operator

Tiemo Communications

02/2017 - 07/2019

Delta State, Nigeria

Software operators.

Achievements/Tasks

- Installing, Updating and Configuring Software Applications.
- Perform Data Recovery in case of system failures or data loss.
- Perform basic hardware maintenance, such as replacing faulty components or upgrading hardware as needed.

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

"My Month Challenge Application" (02/2024 - 03/2024)

 Developed a month challenge Application using Django, HTML, CSS and SQLite Database

MY Website and Blog Post (02/2024 - Present)

 Currently building a full-functional Website that will be link to a blog Post using Django, Flask, HTML, CSS, Database

CERTIFICATES

Python Back-end Professions (08/2023 - Present)

LANGUAGES

English German
Professional Working Proficiency Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Coding and Programming GYM Sports

Listening to Music